John Kanji - Curriculum Vitae

jkanji@dgp.toronto.edu

Profile

I am a Computer Science Masters' student studying at the University of Toronto. I am currently working on applying machine learning techniques to problems in computer animation. I have experience in programming with Python, using the SciPy numerical programming stack, and the PyTorch machine learning framework. I also have strong problem solving and communication skills. I am keen to develop my knowledge and research skills while making real contributions to industry and academia.

Education

University of Toronto - MSc Computer Science (2017-Present)

Courses Included:

- Human-Computer Interaction A+
- Computational Design and Fabrication A+
- Interaction and Perception in AR/VR A+
- Object Modelling and Recognition A

University of York - BSc Computer Science with Industrial Placement (2013-2017)

Courses Included:

- Vision and Graphics 79%
- Computer Vision 73%
- Artificial Intelligence 78%
- Numerical Analysis 78%

Comberton Sixth Form (2011-2013)

A-Levels: Mathematics (A), Further Mathematics (B), Physics (B)

AS-Level: Computing (A)

Attended Villiers Park Residential Course in Computer Science (2013), a one-week course which involved classes and projects on topics in computing, including cryptography and machine learning.

Work Experience

Teaching Assistant - University of Toronto (2017-Present)

Duties included preparing and delivering tutorials and labs, and marking exams and assignments.

Taught courses:

- CSC207 Software Design
- CSC418 Computer Graphics

Treasurer - Computer Science Graduate Students' Union, University of Toronto (2018-Present)

Responsible for all financial matters, including preparing budgets and grant applications.

Sandwich Placement Year - Wellcome Trust Sanger Institute (2015-2016)

Full-stack web development and maintenance of a laboratory information management system webapp in Java, Spring MVC, HTML, Sass, and Javascript. Involved communicating with users and implementing features independently and as part of a team.

Skills

Technical

- Strong grasp of mathematical theory of computing in the areas of predicate logic, set theory and grammars
- Machine Learning Experience with applying neural network machine learning to research problems using PyTorch, and Tensorflow
- Python 7 Years experience including projects making heavy use of the SciPy numerical programming stack.
- Java Experience in Enterprise Java web server development using the Spring MVC framework, and Java 8 functional techniques
- Web development Experience of Javascript, including jQuery, and with HTML, CSS, and Sass
- SQL Experience with Oracle databases, writing SQL and PL/SQL, and schema design
- Version Control with SVN and Git Other:
- Operating Systems Microsoft Windows, Apple OS X, Linux
- Applications Matlab, Microsoft Office

Other Skills

• Intermediate Spanish and basic French and Swedish

Activities and Interests

- Projectionist at York Student Cinema
- Digital art Experience of 3D art software including Blender, Maya and ZBrush
- Electronic Music Production Created songs using the software Logic Pro X

References

Prof David I.W. Levin diwlevin@cs.toronto.edu Dynamic Graphics Project, University of Toronto 40 St George St, Toronto, ON, Canada, M5S 2E4 Dr Mike Freeman, Teaching Fellow mike.freeman@york.ac.uk Department of Computer Science, University of York, Deramore Lane, Heslington, York, United Kingdom, YO10 5GH